optionetics.com 2006-06-15

# Optionetics

Options involve risk. Prior to buying or selling an option, an investor must receive a copy of [Characteristics and Risks of Standardized Options](http://www.cboe.com/Resources/Intro.asp). Investors need a broker to trade options, and must meet suitability requirements. Past results are not necessarily indicative of future performance.

All examples are exclusive of commissions, interest and dividends. You should consult your tax consultant and read the Options Disclosure Document (ODD) prior to investing in options. You can obtain a copy of the ODD from Optionetics, or from the Options Clearing Corporation (1888-options), One North Wacker Drive, Suite 500, Chicago IL 60606.

This Web Site is not designed or intended for Hong Kong, United Kingdom, Australian or New Zealand based investors. 

The information and data contained in this website (Optionetics.com) was obtained from sources believed to be reliable, but accuracy is not guaranteed. Neither the information, nor any opinion expressed, constitutes a recommendation to purchase or sell a security, or to provide investment advice.

The information contained on this site is provided for general informational purposes, as a convenience to the customers of Optionetics. The materials are not a substitute for obtaining professional advice from a qualified person, firm or corporation. Consult the appropriate professional advisor for more complete and current information. Optionetics, Inc. ("Optionetics") is not engaged in rendering any legal or professional services by placing these general informational materials on this website.

Optionetics specifically disclaims any liability, whether based in contract, tort, strict liability or otherwise, for any direct, indirect, incidental, consequential, or special damages arising out of or in any way connected with access to or use of the site, even if Optionetics has been advised of the possibility of such damages, including liability in connection with mistakes or omissions in, or delays in transmission of, information to or from the user, interruptions in telecommunications connections to the site or viruses.

Optionetics makes no representations or warranties about the accuracy or completeness of the information contained on this website. Any links provided to other server sites are offered as a matter of convenience and in no way are meant to imply that Optionetics endorses, sponsors, promotes or is affiliated with the owners of or participants in those sites, or endorses any information contained on those sites, unless expressly stated.

Optionetics is the copyright owner of all text and graphics contained on this website, except as otherwise indicated. Other parties' trademarks and service marks that may be referred to herein are the property of their respective owners. You may print a copy of the information contained herein for your personal use only, but you may not reproduce or distribute the text or graphics to others or substantially copy the information on your own server, or link to this website, without prior written permission of Optionetics. Permission to use and reproduce documents and related graphics available from this website is granted, provided that: 1. the below copyright notice appears in all copies and that both the copyright and this permission notice appear; 2. use and reproduction of documents and related graphics available from this website is limited to personal, non-commercial use; 3. no documents or related graphics, including logos, available from this website are modified in any way; and 4. no graphics, including logos, available from this website are used separate from accompanying text. Use or reproduction for any other purpose is expressly prohibited by law, and may result in civil and criminal penalties.

Violators will be prosecuted to the maximum extent possible.

Terms & Conditions of Online Sales

Optionetics makes every effort to ensure the accuracy of the information published on our Web site. However, the documents and graphics published on this site may contain technical inaccuracies or typographical errors. Optionetics makes no representations about the suitability of the information and graphics presented on this site. All such documents and graphics are provided "as is" without warranty of any kind. 

If an error is made and a product is listed at an incorrect price, Optionetics shall maintain the right to refuse or cancel any orders placed at the incorrect price. If the order has been confirmed and charged to your credit card, Optionetics shall immediately issue a credit in the amount of the incorrect price. 

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Revised and posted as of: May 11, 2006

Optionetics.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following statement to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of the Optionetics.com Web site. The Optionetics.com Web site is owned and operated by Optionetics, Inc. 

Your privacy is important to us. We do not share your information with non-affiliated companies. If you have any questions regarding our privacy statement, please feel free to contact us by e-mail at privacy@optionetics.com.

**Gathering of Information**

_Voluntary Submission_

Optionetics.com does not collect personally identifying information about any individual Optionetics.com Web site user except when knowingly provided by such individual. For example, we may ask you for information when you register to receive a newsletter or to use our online stock and options portfolio. You always have the option not to provide the information we request. If you choose not to provide the information we request, you can still visit most of the Optionetics.com Web site, but you may be unable to access certain options and services.

_Cookies_

A cookie is a data file that certain Web sites write to your computer's hard drive when you visit such sites. A cookie file can contain information, such as a user identification code, that the site uses to track the pages you have visited. Optionetics.com uses cookies solely to track user traffic patterns throughout the Optionetics.com Web site and to allow you access to "member only" section of the site. We use this data on an anonymous basis and we do not correlate this information with personal data of any user.

Most Web site browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to display a warning before accepting a cookie, or to refuse all cookies. However, if you choose to disable the receipt of cookies from our Web site, you may not be able to use certain features of the site. 

_Browser Level Information_

Optionetics.com Web servers automatically collect information about a site user's IP address, browser type and referrer by reading this information from the user's browser (information provided by every user's browser). This information is collected in a database and used--in an aggregated, anonymous manner--in our internal analysis of traffic patterns within our Web site. This information is automatically logged by most Web sites.

**Use of Information**

Our primary goal in collecting user information is to enhance your experience on our Web site. We achieve this goal by, among other things, providing interactive communications such as our electronic newsletters to the e-mail address that you provide to us, and developing future editorial content based on your interests. To develop content targeted to your interests, we use aggregated user information to determine which areas of our Web site users prefer based upon traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but instead how well each page or content area performs overall.

Optionetics.com is a free Web site and we derive revenues from advertising. In order to attract and retain advertisers we use the aggregated, anonymous information that we gather (as well as information from third-party market researchers) to describe our services to partners and to assist our advertisers and sponsors to better understand our audience. This is essential to keeping our service free of charge to our users. We do not disclose personally identifying information about our users to these parties.

Optionetics.com may also disclose information about our users when we believe, in good faith, that the disclosure is required by law. 

When you are on an area of Optionetics.com and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with Optionetics.com as well as business partners and vendors providing hosting and other services for Optionetics.com. If you do not want your information to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer of your information by not using that particular service. These parties, as well as advertisers who contract directly with a third-party service to serve their advertisements, may set their own cookies. 

In addition, any personally identifiable information provided by our users as part of an advertiser promotion online may be provided directly to advertisers.

Please be aware that Optionetics.com sponsors, advertisers or Web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those parties and Web sites linked to Optionetics.com are not covered by this privacy statement. Optionetics.com users should also be aware that, when you voluntarily disclose personal information in chat areas or bulletin boards, that information may be collected by others and may result in unsolicited messages from others. 

Kids under 13: Do not send any information about yourself to us--including information such as your name, address, or e-mail address. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. In the event that we learn we have collected any personal information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as possible.

Hong Kong, United Kingdom, Australian and New Zealand

This website and its contents are directed to US residents and citizens. They are not directed at residents or citizens of the Hong Kong, United Kingdom, Australia or New Zealand. As such, the contents of this Website have not been issued or approved by either the regulatory authorities of or any person authorized to undertake regulated activities in the Hong Kong, United Kingdom, Australia or New Zealand under, respectively, the Securities and Futures Ordinance, the Financial Services and Markets Act 2000, the Corporations Act 2001 or the Companies Act 1993\. Notwithstanding the above, any views expressed in this website are not to be taken as advice or a recommendation to buy or sell any investment and users must make their own decisions based on their own investigations and consultation with their financial adviser or other professional expert. 

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions regarding our privacy statement, please feel free to contact us by e-mail at 

[privacypolicy@optionetics.com](mailto:privacypolicy@optionetics.com). 

This statement may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.

**DEFINITIONS:**

 _Browser type_ : A user's browser is a software program running on a computer that allows users to access documents on the World Wide Web. Browsers can be either text or graphic. They read HTML coded pages that reside on a server and interpret the coding into what the user sees as Web pages. Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer are examples of Web browsers. Browser type typically discloses hardware platform, operating system, and browser software and version. _Referrer_ : The referrer is the URL of the Internet resource or page that causes a browser to request a page or image from Optionetics.com servers. _IP address_ : Every computer connected to the Internet has a numeric address called an "IP address." This may or may not correspond uniquely to a particular computer. In some cases, IP addresses can be resolved to domain names, which may indicate a site visitor's Internet service provider, employer, university, etc. As part of its database analysis Optionetics.com resolves IP addresses to domain names.

For more information on general rules concerning the use of customer data, go to [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

_Optionetics is a trade mark (TM) of Optionetics, Inc. All rights reserved._
